http://www.chfriends.org.uk/privacy-policy

People & Events
Privacy PolicyCHISWICK HOUSE FRIENDS PRIVACY POLICYFor Chiswick House Friends (CHF) members and visitors to CHF’s website and the Chiswick House Dog Show website and visitors thereto.We take the matter of protecting and respecting your privacy very seriously and this Policy explains how this is achieved.We may change this Policy from time to time and therefore will update this page accordingly.Any questions regarding this Policy and our privacy practices should be sent by email to secretary@chfriends.org.ukWho are we?We are an independent charity, registered number 289907, and the registered address is Chiswick House, Burlington Lane, Chiswick, London W4 2RP. The CHF Committee of Trustees determines all activities of CHF and our charity objective is to support Chiswick House and Gardens – financially and by other means – whilst representing the interests of our members and other members of the community.What type of information do we collect from you?The personal information we collect may include your name, address, email address, telephone number and, where applicable, IP address, when you either complete a hard copy CHF Membership Form, register for Membership on-line or use our contact facilities on-line.  If you complete a Standing Order form for membership, your banking information is not held by us, nor is any banking information entered by you on-line if you select payment through our third party processor, who specialises in the secure online capture and processing of financial transactions. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.How is your information used?We hold your information for the legitimate purpose of managing the activities of CHF and we may use your information to:process your initial and subsequent annual membership feesend you communications, if you are a CHF member, by email or by post regarding CHF and Chiswick House and Gardens events and news, plus any local events or matters of legitimate interest for our members.respond to communications from, and correspondence with, anyone volunteering or wishing to provide a service, for our annual Dog Show, or for any other matter you may wish to raise.Erasure or Amendment of your informationYou may contact us at any time to advise us that:you require details of all information CHF holds on you.we do not send emails or letters to your membership address(es). This would, of course, mean that you would not receive any CHF or related news from us. Should you request this, and remain a member of CHF, then we shall retain your personal information for membership and Gift Aid purposes.you wish to resign your membership of CHF. Your personal information, both hard copy and electronic, including any correspondence between us, will then be securely destroyed within three years.as a non-member of CHF, having made contact for either an event or other purpose, you do not wish us to retain the correspondence in any form, in which event CHF will securely destroy all such personally identifiable details on request.We review our retention periods for personal information on a regular basis.  We are legally required to hold some types of information to fulfil our statutory obligations (for example the collection of Gift Aid). However, should you notify us of your resignation or should you fail to renew your annual subscription, all your personal records, both hard copy and electronic will be securely destroyed within 3 years.  During this period, your records will remain secure and unused by us or any third party, except for the collection of Gift Aid.Third Party Providersworking on our behalfCHF uses MailChimp to process electronic mailings. We only share email addresses with MailChimp.  Their privacy statement is available on their websitehttps://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/We may also pass your details to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, or conducting our business.  However when we use these services we disclose only the personal information necessary for the legitimate purpose of managing our electronic affairs and we have contracts with them which require them to keep your information secure and not to use it for their own marketing purposes.We assure you that we do not release your personally-identifiable information beyond the CHF Committee of Trustees and the CHF Dog Show Committee – comprised of individuals authorised by the CHF Committee to manage the annual Dog Show – except as under the previous paragraph  -unless we are required to do so by law, for example by a court order or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime.We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.When you give us personal information, we take appropriate steps to ensure that it is treated securely. Non –sensitive details (your email address etc.) are transmitted normally over the Internet and this can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure.  As a result, whilst we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.  Once we receive your information we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.  You should be aware that, if you use our services whilst you are outside the EU, your information may be transferred outside the EU in order to provide you with the information you have requested.Third Party LinksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website, related to the objectives of CHF.  These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.Use of CookiesCookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser, if you allow, that enables the site’s or service provider’s system to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.We use cookies to track your progress through the site and to understand and save your preferences for future visits.Children aged below 13 years.We are concerned to protect the privacy of children, as with all our information.  For children below the age of 13 years we require their parent/guardian’s permission beforehand whenever they wish to provide us with personal information.Your ConsentBy using our site, you agree to our website’s privacy policyChanges to our Privacy PolicyShould we change our privacy policy we shall post those changes on this page.Date 25th May 2018
